[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[newscaster] If you've seen
new street art, you're not alone.
The provocative murals have been
popping up all around the city.
[Fisk] Sometimes,
peace needs to be broken.
I wanna see my tío.
[Fisk] Chaos must reign...
[Devlin] Hands in the fucking air!
[Fisk] ...just for a moment,
to build a stronger order.
This port is a black eye
on the face of this city.
I think we can do better.
[Vanessa] I sent Buck to Luca
to tell him to pay Viktor
1.8 restitution
- for the hijacking.
- [gunshot]
[Heather] I thought we might spend
some time on something we need
- to get out into the open.
- Adam.
Wilson, did you confront this man?
[Fisk] Yes.
I did tell him how I felt about you.
That I couldn't fathom
a life of meaning without her.
[Heather] Forgiveness isn't just
the highest act of love,
it is the only way forward.
[Adam] Please!
[Heather] And where is Adam now?
Let me out!
[♪ dramatic music playing]
As graffiti artists, we get this bad rep
that we're hurting the city,
but there's dangerous people out there
that are actually hurting
the civilians of New York City,
and people like the vigilantes
are helping them.
[BB] Is there law and order in New York?
My friend sent me this video...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, check this out.
Bro, look how crazy that is.
Like, where do you learn that?
Kinda looks like a swordsman.
Swordsman, if you're watching this,
keep doing the good work,
because our cops here...
they don't really do much, so...
[♪ eerie music playing]
[♪ eerie music intensifies]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
"Thou did establish Saint Ives as a judge
in the midst of his brethren,
"making him a friend
and advocate of the poor.
"Do thou make us, by his intercession,
steadfast in the pursuit of justice,
"confident in that merciful goodness."
"Through Christ our Lord..."
[Karen] ...get you help.
You just have to stay awake.
No, no, no.
[gun cocks]
[crowd gasps]
[Matt] "Who lives and reigns with you
in the unity of the Holy Spirit."
[church bell tolling]
[chains rattling]
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[♪ music intensifies]
[grunting, screaming]
- [muted screams]
- [glass breaking]
[both screaming, grunting]
- [thuds]
- [crowd gasps]
[Karen] No, Foggy! No!
[Karen cries]
"Amen."
[breath trembles]
What are you doing?
[inhales deeply] Ah, you know,
just checkin' in.
You pray? Still?
[Matt] Yeah. I've stopped a few times
over the years, but...
always end up coming back to it.
So, you'll volunteer
at The Bowery Mission until 4:00.
Then back to Gracie Mansion,
and then the Children's Art Fund
benefit's at 7:00.
That sounds nice.
You go then.
I'm tired of these black tie events.
[Sheila] I very much doubt
that's an option.
Just so you know, you have
an unscheduled visitor in your office.
There he is.
Mr. Mayor.
What are you doing here?
[Luca] That any way
to greet an old friend?
[♪ tense music playing]
I've got this.
- [Heather] You all right?
- Yeah, sure. Why?
Um... You go to a bank
and get taken hostage?
Oh, right, yeah, that. Sure.
- Yeah, that.
- That worked out.
[chuckles softly] Matt,
you were a victim of a crime.
Sure, I understand.
I'm just saying that I...
I... I knew I was gonna be okay.
[exhales] I can't really explain it.
It was just like...
- Faith.
- Something like that.
[chuckles softly] Thank you, though.
[Fisk] You've got five minutes.
[Luca chuckles] Look at all these books.
You haven't read a single one of 'em,
have you?
Is this about the 1.8?
It's all a show. The whole thing, right?
Might as well be
Halloween in here. [chuckles]
Four minutes and thirty seconds.
[Luca] Come on.
Is that how we're gonna do this?
No foreplay?
- Ugh, I'm late.
- [Matt] Early patient this morning?
I'm meeting with my editor. Remember?
Oh, that's right.
The, uh, congratulatory breakfast.
She's already putting the screws in me
about my next book.
[chuckles] Wow, that's quick.
- Mmm.
- [Matt] Well...
if you need help spit-balling ideas,
you know where to find me.
Interesting you should ask.
I've told you the premise, right?
Uh, maybe?
Vigilantes.
Why we revere the mask.
I get it, cool. Yeah, interesting.
Yeah. I think so.
You need to give Viktor the 1.8.
And I'll give you
until the end of the week.
Respectfully, Mr. Mayor,
you can shove that 1.8 up your ass.
[metal clanking]
Make it 2.8.
1.8 to Viktor,
and the balance to me, of course.
I-- I-- I think
it's a fascinating question.
What about a mask?
Does it hide us
and give us permission to do things
that are legally and socially taboo,
like violence?
I mean, does a mask allow us
to be our true selves,
or does it strip away our identity
and allow us to act like animals?
Hmm, yeah.
Uh, I don't know. Maybe... maybe both.
Maybe, right?
You have experience with those people,
don't you?
With animals?
Vigilantes.
- You've represented a few, right?
- Ooh.
What, are you researching me now?
You're out of the game, old man.
Stay out of it.
[Heather] Well, I've been thinking,
maybe you would consider
setting me up with someone like,
I don't know, Frank Castle?
[laughs]
The Punisher? You wanna...
You wanna interview The Punisher?
- [chuckles softly]
- Bad idea?
No, it's like--
That's a solid, solid idea.
You've got 'till the end of the week.
Your time's up.
See ya, Fisk. Give your wife my regards.
Please show him out.
[chuckles softly] Okay.
Um, how about Daredevil?
- You've worked with him, right?
- [cell phone buzzes]
[sighs] Oh, shit, that's my Uber.
All right.
Don't be weird.
I'm not gonna stalk your clients,
- but maybe we can talk about it after?
- Sure.
- Hmm?
- Of course.
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ theme music playing]
[♪ theme music continues playing]
- [vehicles passing]
- [horns honking]
- [pigeon coos]
- [people talking indistinctly]
[Sheila] Mr. Mayor, it's urgent. Come.
This is John Santini from Sanitation.
Uh, call me Johnny. Hey, it's a pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Mayor.
I work at the Sanitation. 35 years.
Happy to have you, Johnny.
Just want to let you know,
I voted for you.
I can't tell you what a pleasure it is
to actually be here.
Mr. Santini, if you would tell the Mayor
why you're here today.
Oh... Right, right. The--The mural.
I got bad news and worse news, Mr. Mayor.
I thought that we took care of this.
[Sheila sighs]
Nah, turns out,
it's gonna be a lot tougher
to get that down than we thought.
Why is that?
Well, look,
I made a real good run at that wall.
I got the biggest power washer,
'cause I didn't wanna ruin the facade.
Didn't do squat.
So, I made a switch.
I switched to a 50-50 sandglass,
like a concentration.
- It was the only way to go.
- You should get to the point.
Oh, no, you don't understand.
See, the mural, it's made with this epoxy,
so I had to do a chemical analysis.
- Then I had to get this special solvent...
- Johnny.
- ...from my guy in Philly--
- Just tell him what you told me.
The worst news.
Right. It's blood.
The mural. It's made outta human blood.
[♪ eerie suspenseful music playing]
Get Gallo in here. Now.
- Your strategy?
- [sighs]
Well, essentially, poison counsel.
- Really?
- [Matt] Yeah. You heard it here first.
You know, Madison hired Cready,
Glaughlin, and McKagan
to guide him through
a complicated yet sophisticated accounting
of his new
and uncharted business model,
and while they may be the city's
preeminent tax law firm,
they were in over their heads.
Wow, so you're literally
pointing the finger at his attorneys.
Have you met the fine gentlemen
at Cready, Glaughlin, and McKagan?
Oh, I have. And I approve.
- [chuckles]
- What is she doing here?
Who?
[Kirsten] The Ayala girl.
Hey, it's good to see you.
- Is everything all right?
- [Angela] Yeah.
I was hoping to talk to Mr. Murdock.
Of course. Yeah, come in, come in.
Uh... do you mind?
Uh... Okay.
- I'll just be in my office.
- Cool. We'll pick this up.
[Matt] Thanks.
- Hi.
- [softly] Hi.
So, 11:17 a.m., what is that,
third period? Fourth?
History? Biology?
- [Angela] English, actually.
- Oh.
I'm getting a 99.
One-oh-four if you factor in the curve.
[laughs]
He was onto something, Matt.
He was investigating something.
[Hector] Someone's gotta
protect the streets.
People are going missing.
No one seems to care.
[metal rattling]
[Angela] I don't know for sure,
but I think it had something to do
with all those people going missing.
All those kidnappings.
He started tracking them.
Angela, I know you're upset
and you have every right to be.
But this isn't safe, I--
Don't tell me how to be, Mr. Murdock.
Mmm-mmm. Not now.
[voice shaking] Don't pull that
therapy talk that I'm processing,
or trying to control, or whatever.
Or that I should be in school because
that's what Hector would have wanted.
This is what he would have wanted.
Someone finishing his work.
Someone actually doing something for once.
[sighs]
Therapy talk? Was I doing that?
Straight up. [chuckles]
And I hate that shit.
[chuckles] Yeah, sure. Kinda hate it, too.
All those kidnappings
were all close to the old Q line.
The one they shut down. Track 61.
[sighs]
Look, Angela,
I'm just a lawyer, all right?
I tried to help your uncle in court,
but something like this,
that's for the police.
The police killed my uncle.
[chuckling] I'm not going to them.
All right, fair enough, fair enough,
but what do you want me to do about it?
[♪ tense music playing]
Um...
How about literally anything, Mr. Murdock?
Attorney at law.
Big fancy office,
here to help the little guy, right?
Only on your terms.
'Cause when the little guy
puts something for real in your hands,
you're all, "Nah."
That's fine.
[clicks tongue] That's cool.
My bad for thinking you cared.
It's not that simple, Angela.
- It's not how this works.
- [chuckles]
You know what?
My uncle, two days before he got shot,
you know what he told me?
He told me,
"Don't rely on anyone
to do what you can do for yourself."
Damn, he was right.
[sighs]
- [train rattling]
- [traffic bustling]
[♪ tense dramatic music playing]
[Gallo] He mixes blood into the paint
and then applies the epoxy on top.
It makes the murals
essentially impervious.
How many murals in total?
Twelve confirmed, with 18 known IDs,
but we've gathered at least
five unique DNA profiles for each mural.
And at five DNA profiles per mural,
we estimate at least 60 victims.
It's difficult to project just yet.
Testing is underway on what we now suspect
may be some...
earlier pieces in his evolution
and more victims.
[Sheila] Missing reports are up...
[echoing] ...but this can't account
for all of them.
[Angie, echoing] Sir, we also know
that he somehow managed to avoid detection
by any of the city's surveillance footage.
[Sheila] You have to do better than that.
[Angie] Based on the size
and the scope of the murals...
[clock thudding loudly]
- [imperceptible]
- [loud thudding continues]
Someone else could die 'cause they didn't
know there was a serial killer on the--
- Trust me. I know what I'm doing.
- [laughing]
[thudding stops]
[sighs]
[clicks tongue] Sound an alarm,
and he could lay low for a while.
He could wait us out.
Then he'll come back harder
and stronger. No.
Not a single word leaves this room.
This is no way to run a goddamn railroad.
When the Sanitation Department
figures out there's a serial killer
before the NYPD does,
maybe it's time
to switch up the protocols.
[♪ JJ Wiseboy "Bow Down" playing]
♪ I've been waiting
for my moment to blow ♪
♪ I'm ready to show the globe
that I'm one of the GOATs ♪
♪ Say what you want ♪
♪ But I know that you won't approach
as the enemy a plot on my throne... ♪
- [canister rattling]
- [spraying]
[women laugh]
[woman 1] Hey, are you Muse?
Is it cool if we take a picture of you?
[woman 2] Not-- Not a selfie, though.
Just like, artist, his work,
you know. [chuckles softly]
[♪ eerie dramatic music playing]
[women scream]
Luca came to see me.
It was very disrespectful, might I add.
To the Mayor's office?
- [Fisk] Hmm.
- Huh.
That's bold.
[Fisk] That's what I thought as well.
And as we imagined, he...
[inhales deeply] ...he has no intentions
of paying his debt. [sighs]
So, I... added a million dollars tax
to his bill.
- [laughs]
- Viktor will like that.
If Luca ever pays up.
I don't need Viktor to like it.
I need him to want it.
Badly.
[Vanessa] Mmm.
Vanessa, you know, politics, it's...
it's a different type of problem solving.
Most of it is new to me,
but some things, they remain unchanged.
Find what a person wants,
then either withhold it
or provide it...
and they'll do anything.
Not tonight.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
You're asking New York's elite for money.
[indistinct conversation]
I hope that everything works out for you.
[Sheila] Mr. Mayor.
Michael, it's great to see you.
[Vanessa] Sure, they want influence,
but they don't need it.
[laughter]
[Vanessa] It's like selling a Basquiat
to a billionaire. [chuckles softly]
It's all just... ego and vanity.
[woman] That is a curious first endeavor
you've identified, Wilson.
This port project,
it's not just a first endeavor.
Well, tell us then. What is it again?
It's a engine of industry, is what it is.
It moves growth quickly.
It's got a lotta horsepower,
if you understand.
Most would say
I'm the determining factor in that sector.
Oh...
[Vanessa] By simply being there
and asking them for money,
you're giving them all they care about.
He's taking me up Madison. I saw them...
This was, as I'm sure you know, one of--
Certain ways we operate here, Wilson.
Reassurance of their supremacy.
[Jack] These changes you're making
with the police,
this obsession you have with vigilantes,
it's just not gonna work.
Whether you can do it or not
isn't the issue here, Wilson.
I'm surprised
you'd even raise that specter.
What we're talking about here is buy-in.
This project simply...
doesn't align with our interests.
I've been told.
And it's Mr. Mayor to you.
Why don't we be honest
with each other here?
I didn't realize that was on the table.
I'd like nothing more.
You've made a substantial amount of your
fortune around the port, haven't you?
I've had many business interests...
in my career.
[woman] And many associates along the way.
[Fisk] What are you suggesting?
I'm saying your port expansion project
is a self-serving con, Mr. Mayor.
You're using taxpayer dollars
to further enrich yourself.
[man] And your colleagues, so to speak.
You know, I've--
I always put the city before myself.
And if you're suggesting
anything different,
well, that's just nonsense.
[woman] You may have a seat
at the table right now,
for a couple of years anyway,
but the people in this room
still decide who gets to eat.
I suggest you don't lose sight of that.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Tell your wife the flowers
were exquisite tonight, if you would.
The people that actually make it happen,
they don't sit around and wait.
People in this room... they...
They know nothing about that.
Underestimate the people in this room
at your own peril.
They may not use garrotes
- or cement shoes.
- [chuckles]
One phone call to the right person,
and well...
Bye-bye, Gracie Mansion.
That's a threat?
[chuckling] No.
No, no, no, it's, uh... It's a warning.
- [Vanessa gasps]
- [Fisk] Oh.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
It seems my suits aren't fitting
like they were.
I guess we have to get you
a new wardrobe, then.
[man over recording] ...Astoria.
It is rumored dating back to the 1800s...
Workin' late?
[man] Presently,
Track 61 is used as a storage...
[Matt] I hope that's not for you.
...and a van.
Oh boy.
What's up?
- [glass clinks]
- [Cherry sighs]
[heart beating rapidly]
Cherry, what is it?
You're gonna hear about it anyway,
but I-- I'd rather you hear it from me.
- Okay.
- I got a call from my guy at the precinct.
Said there's a serial killer out there.
They're going through a DEFCON scenario.
How many victims?
Cherry?
What? How-- How many?
Upwards of 60, so they say.
They've identified a suspect, though.
- Who is it?
- Graffiti artist,
paintin' walls all around town.
Goes by the name "Muse."
Apparently...
Apparently what?
[♪ tense music playing]
[Cherry] He paints
with his victims' blood.
- [Matt exhales sharply]
- [Cherry grunts softly]
[Cherry sighs]
Matt...
you gotta be straight with me, buddy.
You gotta let this one go.
Just let the police do their jobs.
[sniffs, clears throat]
[♪ tense music continues playing]
[door opens]
[people talking indistinctly]
[Fisk] These people are like parasites.
Can't they see how important
this port project is?
- [Buck] Sir.
- Hi.
- [man] Vanessa, this way, this way.
- [Vanessa] Yes.
There's something you need to see.
Very nice to see you.
Yes, I remember Brian, of course.
Vanessa.
I'm sorry, but there's pressing business.
Can you make my apologies for me?
Yes, of course.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Buck] These came straight
from the forensic team, sir.
[♪ eerie music playing]
Man's obviously mocking the police.
We can use this.
- [man] Marker.
- [BB] Do you feel safe on the streets?
I ain't supposed to say nothin',
but I hear two girls have gone missing.
I mean, nobody really knows
what happened to them,
but when you go missing
down here in the city,
everyone knows something is up.
We hear that there's one girl
or a couple girls found dead,
but they're drained out of their blood.
We really need someone out here to,
like, protect us,
'cause, baby,
I don't feel safe out here.
[Gallo] This is ridiculous.
I've got a serial killer on the loose,
you cut the force's overtime,
and now I need to report to you
on the Muse case?
Well, I care about this city.
Then put more cops on the street!
That's exactly why I asked you here.
I intend to.
A task force.
Hand-picked by me.
[Gallo] This is every bad apple
in the barrel.
Yes, it appears your officers
have a subculture amongst them.
People like to use the word "gang."
I prefer "motivated individuals."
And due to the extreme nature
of these crimes,
this task force will have special powers
and privileges...
- Like overtime.
- [scoffs]
And... no body cameras.
That sort of thing.
Ah... And who the hell's
gonna oversee this?
Like I said, I care about the city.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
- [Powell] ...last week, right?
- [Cole] Yeah.
- [Powell] We gotta make that pickup.
- [Cole] No, we don't.
- [Powell] We're not gonna get that guy...
- [Cole chuckles] Stop.
[Fisk] This city is in a crisis.
A serial killer is roaming our streets.
He needs to be stopped!
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Okay, but, uh, why us?
Because some of you...
You're victims of bad luck.
Others, you've been a little overzealous.
But all of you, throughout your careers,
have shown initiative.
Sergeant Cole North.
Yes, sir.
Born and raised in Chicago,
top of your class in the Academy,
made Detective in only three years.
That's quite impressive.
Yet here you are in New York.
You lost it all.
Tell us what happened January 14th.
I was responding to a call,
possible drug activity in the park.
Upon my arrival,
I saw a guy hand an 11-year-old some oxy.
The guy denied everything.
So, I... encouraged him
to tell the truth.
Captain didn't see it that way.
There's a lotta shitbags
in the world, sir.
Now there's a lot less of 'em.
Yes, that-- that's right.
- Sometimes...
- [officers talking indistinctly]
...when you need to get the job done,
it requires a little...
well, creative thinking.
I assume Gallo has told you
that we have a serial killer in our midst.
I want to be clear.
I've brought you here
because of your skills.
Because of your ability to get results.
Consider yourself founding members
of my Anti-Vigilante Task Force.
Buck?
- [lock unclasping]
- [door rattles]
This killer, Muse, he wears a mask.
Well, that's because he's afraid.
I don't want you to be afraid.
I want you to show your faces,
because you are New York's finest,
- and this city is yours!
- [officers muttering in agreement]
And you're not gonna
let some masked criminals
take it away from you!
- [all] Yeah!
- Isn't that right?
[cheering, applauding]
Okay.
[♪ dramatic music intensifies]
[train rattling]
- [steam hissing]
- [traffic bustling]
[train thudding rhythmically]
[breathing rapidly]
[rats squeaking]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ tense music intensifies]
[metal rattling loudly]
[rats squeaking]
[footsteps approaching]
[man speaking indistinctly
over speaker]
Designed to ferry VIPs
to one of New York's luxury hotels.
It is rumored to be an entranceway
to a series of abandoned rail tunnels
dating back to the 1800s.
- [cell phone vibrates]
- [automated voice] Call from Ayala Home.
Answer or decline?
Call from Ayala--
- Hello?
- Matt? It's Soledad.
I'm sorry to call you so late.
No, Soledad, it's fine.
What's-- What's goin' on?
[Soledad] It's Angela. She still hasn't
come home. That's not like her.
Has she been in touch with you?
She told me
she was going to see you, Matt.
I'm worried. I'm so worried.
She's never done this before.
I didn't know who else to call.
She's never--
It's okay. Soledad, it's okay.
Just stay where you are.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- [sighs]
- [call ringing]
[female operator] 911,
what is your emergency?
Hello?
Hello? 911.
Fuck it.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[lock clicking]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[cable whooshing]
[muffled rattling]
[rattling intensifies]
[♪ tense music playing]
[unzipping]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[metal clanking]
[♪ eerie music continues]
[breathing rapidly]
[train rattling]
[grunts]
[muted thudding]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[footsteps ricocheting]
[breath trembles]
[breathing rapidly]
[Adam panting]
[Fisk] I can imagine that Vanessa
would like for me to let you go.
[Adam] Thank you.
Thank you!
But that's a difficult thing for me to do.
You understand that, right?
How we are... locked together.
[♪ tense, dramatic music playing]
Our experience... shared.
And... when I was younger, smaller,
I went up against men three times my size.
Yeah.
Men who knew how to use their hands,
and they did so, often.
And I learned that...
a simple tool,
it can be a great equalizer.
[axe rattles loudly]
- [machine whirrs]
- [blood squelching]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[metal rattling]
[train rattling]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[metallic whoosh]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Muse grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[heart beating rapidly]
[breathing rapidly]
[screams, grunts]
[both grunting]
[knife clinks]
[tools rattling]
[both grunting]
[heart beating rhythmically]
[groans]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[both grunting]
[blood squelching]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- [grunts]
- [knife clinks]
[both grunting]
- [screams]
- [light clangs]
[Muse groans]
[grunting]
- [electricity crackling]
- [screams]
[both grunting]
[screams]
[grunts]
[screams, grunts]
- [grunts]
- [Adam groans]
[grunting]
[panting]
[blood splashing]
[grunts]
[Daredevil grunts]
[Muse panting]
[Daredevil screams]
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[Fisk grunts]
[Daredevil grunting]
[grunts loudly]
Mine!
- [cable rattling]
- [Muse screaming]
- [strained grunting]
- [gagging]
[heart beating feebly]
[both grunt]
[cable slinks]
- [exhaling rhythmically]
- [thumping]
[Matt] "Thou did establish Saint Ives
as a judge in the midst of his brethren,
"making him a friend
and advocate of the poor.
[Daredevil exhaling rhythmically]
[Matt] "Do thou make us,
by his intercession,
"steadfast in the pursuit of justice
- "and confident in that merciful goodness.
- [rhythmic thumping]
- [Daredevil panting]
- [Matt] "Through Christ our Lord
"who lives and reigns with you
in the unity of the Holy Spirit,
- [Daredevil grunts]
- [gasps]
[Matt] "Amen."
[heart beating rhythmically]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[♪ sweeping choral music playing]
[metallic rattling]
[Angela panting]
[♪ sweeping choral music
continues playing]
- [Daredevil and Angela panting]
- [Angela] Daredevil?
[Daredevil] It's okay. I'm here.
Yeah. I'm here. [breathing rapidly]
[♪ captivating choral music playing]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[♪ somber music playing]
[music fades]